https://www.piu.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy Statement Petersen International Underwriters
Petersen International Underwriters respects your privacy and will never sell, rent, lease, trade or give away your information.
California Consumer Privacy Act
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), gives residents of the state of California the right to prevent businesses from selling their personal information.
Petersen International Underwriters takes your privacy seriously. We do not sell your personal information
If you would like to record your preference that PIU not sell your data in the future, please click here.
Information We May Collect
The non-public personal information that we collect about you includes, but is not limited to:
* Personal information such as name, date of birth, address and contact information;
* Financial information including credit history;
* Health history.
Confidentiality And Security
We take precautions to protect your information both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information that information is encrypted and transmitted in a secure way.
Only our employees and other third parties, who need or who have the legal right to, the information to service your account have access to your personal information.
The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Right to Access Or Correct Your Personal Information
You have a right to request access to, or correction of, your personal information in our possession.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy notice or would like to learn more about how we protect your privacy, please contact the agent or broker who handled this insurance, or our offices at: 23929 Valencia Boulevard, Second Floor, Valencia, California 91355 , Toll Free number: (800)345-8816, E-mail: piu@piu.org
